Hello? Joey?
Hello, Dad?
According to the rider,
Berdugo entered
Santan Woods Subdivision,
the alternate route
to the airfields.
Copy.
All units, please proceed
to Santan Woods Subdivision!
[OBB]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
[VEHICLES REVVING]
Let's split up!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
Berdugo, the police are here!
Damn!
Block them!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Catch them!
Open it!
[GUN FIRING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
Shoot them!
[GUN FIRING]
[BULLETS PLINKING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUN FIRING]
[GUN COCKS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GUN FIRING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Hold on!
[TIRES SCREECH]
[POLICE SIREN WAILING]
What are you doing?
Reverse!
["NEVER SAY DIE"
BY KIM DE LEON PLAYING]
Resist them!
["NEVER SAY DIE"
BY KIM DE LEON PLAYING]
Lower your gun!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUN CLICKING]
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Lower your gun!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Tomas Limjoco, alias Berdugo,
you're under arrest!
- Take him!
- Get down!
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
You animal!
- [THUDDING]
- [INTENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Andrew!
You killed my mother!
- You're an animal!
- Andrew...
Andrew!
This is the end for you,
Berdugo!
You'll rot in prison!
[INTENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrew!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Matias already confessed.
I know what you're doing.
Good cop, bad cop, right?
Classic interrogation tactic.
You separate us,
then tell me he broke.
[BEEPS]
I've been Tomas Limjoco's
right hand for a long time.
He made me pretend
to be Berdugo.
But I couldn't refuse because
he held my family as hostage.
I'm begging you.
Make sure my family is safe.
I'm ready to testify against him
as long as my wife
and children are safe.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
This is the end for you, Tomas.
Do you think this is over?
Do you think I am
the last syndicate you'd chase?
It doesn't matter to me
how many of you are there.
What matters is you're here
in front of me.
There's someone
who wants to talk to you.
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SLAPS]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
That's for my mother.
[SLAPS]
That's for me.
That's for what you did
to my family.
You thought you could control
everything...
The people, the truth...
And even us?
You are not God.
You're a demon!
And you know where you'll rot.
I'm your husband, Yvette.
I love our children.
We're a family!
Family?
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
You have no right
to be a husband.
to be a father.
I'll tell the children
that you're dead.
They will mourn,
but they will move on.
I will make sure
they forget you.
They don't deserve
a father like you!
[SLAPS]
[SINISTER MUSIC PLAYING]
[SINISTER MUSIC CONTINUES]
- Cheers!
- Cheers.
Okay!
So, where's Berdugo?
He's in the provincial jail now.
Good thing Andrew
immediately provided
the evidence Ma'am Rebecca kept.
There's no escape
for that Berdugo anymore.
And he has multiple cases
stacked against him.
Many cases.
Why are you smiling?
What? What are you saying?
Are you going crazy?
Do you want Liza to haunt you?
Cheers!
[PLEASANT MUSIC PLAYING]
- Cheers again.
- Cheers.
Thank you, guys,
Thank you, guys.
You look like
you're about to cry.
- Are you crying?
- You look so sad!
No, no, hey.
What are you saying?
Wait, I'll join you.
What "clingy" are you saying?
You're making false assumptions.
Of course, I'll get ready.
I still have to go home
to the province, you know?
Right.
Oh, before you leave...
Jin Ho, congratulations.
Because you'll be a big help
to the intelligence agency
in Korea
if ever that gets formalized.
Congrats.
Thank you.
Guys, this isn't the last time
we'll see each other, okay?
Of course!
So, we'll just update
each other?
- See you?
- See you.
- Okay, see you.
- Joey.
See you.
Okay.
You're so cute!
[CHUCKLES]
Take care.
- Take care.
- Take care, guys.
- Okay.
[PLEASANT MUSIC CONTINUES]
If Jin Ho...
is thankful to Berdugo...
As for me, I want to thank you.
For helping us find Berdugo.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
It wasn't just me.
It was all of us.
I agree, but I also owe you.
I want to apologize for...
For everything.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
For the things I said...
That you're immature,
too young.
That wasn't true.
You're strong,
principled, and kind.
You're not hard to love, Joey.
But we both know it's not
the right time, right?
I need to focus on my family,
and you need to fix yours.
And...
I still have a lot to do.
I need to graduate.
And you still have work.
Talking about work...
I don't even know if I still
have something to go back to,
after all that happened.
Why?
You know you have nothing
to fear.
I believe you'll get back
on your feet.
And no matter what happens,
I'll still be here.
I'll watch you.
To do what?
Make reaction videos?
Don't you want that?
I need to go home.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
See you around, Boss Budol.
See you around, Joey On Duty.
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC PLAYING]
[EMOTIONAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Take care of this, okay?
The next time we meet
and you're still wearing this...
it would mean something to me.
We'll see.
Okay.
[STIRRING EMOTIONAL
MUSIC PLAYING]
[STIRRING EMOTIONAL MUSIC
CONTINUES]
By the way, the crawlers
that I had edited earlier...
- is it done?
- Done, Madam.
Audio.
Andrew...
We're about to start.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
So? It's your first live
in over a month.
Good luck!
Ready?
We're going live in...
five, four, three, two...
Tirada Express!
[GALVANIZING MUSIC PLAYING]
Good day, Tirada viewers.
Did you miss me?
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC PLAYING]
We have so many questions.
But, that's good.
We should be involved.
Some say...
I have no obligation to explain.
They have a point.
But if you've been watching
for a long time,
you know I don't run away
from questions.
Right?
So, fine.
You'll be Boy Abunda today.
[SENTIMENTAL MUSIC CONTINUES]
And to those who doubt,
thank you too.
You're important because we're
all searching for the truth.
Next time, I'll be more careful,
I'll protect myself more
because it's not just
my name at stake,
but your trust.
And as long as there's truth
to reveal,
Tirada continues!
More fact checks!
Oh, my god!
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Madam, wow!
178,000 viewers!
- Seriously?
- Yes!
Boss!
[WHISPERS]
Saludo viewers, guess
what's happening today!
[CURIOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Oh, good job guessing!
How did you know
I'm graduating?
Yeah!
Wow, I have so many viewers!
Before, there were only
three of you!
Mom! Dad!
Look!
I have 3,000 viewers now!
- Before it was just 3!
- What?
- Let me see!
- Really?
Amazing!
Even...
[GASPS]
- Yes, there's a lot!
- See, so many!
Hello! Hi, everyone!
- 3,000?
- You're right.
Keep supporting Joey, okay?
Thank you, thanks.
Hey, say thank you.
Hello, Saludo viewers!
Thank you so much for supporting
my daughter!
Now there are 3,000
of you watching!
Yeah, thank you!
Please share the live.
- There!
- Anyway, for today's live...
- Let's see.
- I have an announcement...
- to them.
- What?
And to you, Mom and Dad.
- What announcement...
Today, I'll reveal...
my future career.
[UPLIFTING MUSIC PLAYING]
- Career!
- Career?
My god! Is this it?
Career reveal?
There's such a thing?
- No, because...
- Oh, okay.
Many are asking what I'll do
after graduation.
With everything
I've been through,
fighting drugs...
And of course, seeing those
who really dive in to fight.
I was inspired.
So, the career I want is...
I want to be...
a police officer!
Police?
- Oh, police? Look...
- Police?
Look at your mother's face, see?
She looks stressed.
Wait, police?
Why?
Joey, maybe...
you could consider
to be a pulmonologist?
A principal?
A barangay chief!
Joey, police, really?
So, that's why it's Saludo ,
salute!
She wants to be a policewoman!
That's clever, Dad.
If you want to be
a police officer...
Fine, I'll support you.
- Let's support her!
- Wait!
Why don't we vote on it?
But that's really what I want,
Mom.
Do you want my daughter
to be a policewoman?
Do you want her to be...
They want her
to be a policewoman.
- Police, it's police.
- See?
Oh, so many shares.
- You guys...
- So many likes.
Okay, fine.
Police it is!
Go! Support!
If you want to be a police
officer, then police it is.
Oh, you know...
because she'll be
a policewoman...
- Never say die.
[CAMERA SHUTTER SNAPPING]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Tomas Limjoco,
you're under arrest!
You animal!
[THUDDING]
I'll tell the children
that you're dead.
If you think this is the end,
then you're wrong.
I'll come back for you.
You're Berdugo, right?
So, you've been
transferred here?
Nice! Share your goods with me.
I have no supply.
You're so selfish!
Give me some!
I said I have none!
- [GROANING AND GRUNTING]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Get down!
[MAN GROANING]
[GROANS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Where are they?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC PLAYING]
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Andrew...
How are you, Joey On Duty?
[ROMANTIC MUSIC CONTINUES]
Wow.
The badge.
And the bracelet.
Nice combination.
You're still wearing it.
Does it mean that...
Joey!
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC PLAYING]
Jin Ho!
How are you?
Andrew.
Just keep it.
We are undercover, remember?
Bro!
[INQUISITIVE MUSIC CONTINUES]
How are you?
Wait...
I know I'm supposed
to meet Jin Ho and Joey.
Why are you here?
Well, I'm not
the only police here.
Do you want me to show you?
Oh, look at that!
[CHUCKLES]
Wait, wait.
How did that happen?
This isn't even my jurisdiction,
but...
Well, Jin Ho and Joey missed me.
It's okay if you don't.
Andrew misses you.
That's why he teases you.
Maybe...
A bit, just a bit.
It's a pleasure.
Anyways, how about you?
What's your mission here,
Jin Ho?
Actually, we are looking
for a Korean drug lord.
And he has been operating
on an island near here.
Korean drug lord?
- Here?
- Yes.
So, what now?
Let's fight!
Never say die?
Never say die!
Never say die.
- Yes!
["NEVER SAY DIE"
BY JILLIAN WARD PLAYING]